Yes, so we're here. It says, "Hi, nima rasimi. Help us to get to know you."
Most of our writing is for work, academia, or personal, right?
So can I skip this part? It's a little bit uncomfortable.
But whatever. Let's say that I want to write for my academia, right?
And I click Next. What do you plan to use Quilbot before?
So let's say emails, blog and online posts, and research papers as well, right?
And I click Next. Where do you mainly write?
So I mainly write on Word and Google Docs these two.
Who writes on PowerPoint? It's a very weird option to be in Google Sheets.
Come on. What's up? Okay. I click Next.
Protect your writing everywhere. Now, thank you. I don't want to skip.
Get premium skip, and now we are back to Quilbot's homepage.